

Blessing A.

Software Engineer & Blockchain Expert

• Lagos, Nigeria 🔼 2+ Years Experience

Technical Analyst & Developer @ PTPWallet

Contact

Showwcase

https://showwcase.com/seunscape

GitHub

https://github.com/SeunScape

Website

https://blessingalabi-seunscape.vercel.app/

Twitter

https://twitter.com/blerix_

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/blessing-alabi-9090041b1/

About

I am a web developer passionate about blockchain technology. Over the last 5 years, I have been learning and building web applications while studying computer science at the university.

I also garnered interest in blockchain technology early on and have been actively involved in its development. I am a member of various blockchain communities and keep myself updated with the latest trends and developments in the space. I am also a freelance writer and have published several articles on the subject.

I have a solid understanding of various technologies, including Express.js (Node.js framework), React.js (JavaScript framework), Next.js (JavaScript framework), TailwindCSS (Cascading Style Sheets framework), Solidity (programming language for EVM blockchains), Figma (Graphics design | UI/UX), and more.

Skills

Blockchain Senior	HTML Senior	CSS Senior	Javas	Script Senior	React Senior	Solidity Mid-level
WordPress Mid-level	Git Mid-level	Figma	Redux	TypeScript	Tailwind CSS	

Experiences



Technical Analyst & Developer

PTPWallet • December 2021 - Present

I do Wordpress and provide technical content



Upwork Technical Writer

Upwork Inc • December 2020 - Present

Blockchain & crypto technical writer.

Educations / Credentials



Ethereum Blockchain Developer Bootcamp with Solidity 🗷

Udemy • July 2022 - September 2022





CISCO Networking Certificate 🛮

Cisco Networking Academy • January 2022 - January 2022





Blockchain: Beyond the Basics 🗹

LinkedIn Learning • June 2021 - July 2021

